University of Arizona 75th anniversary papers, 1959-1961
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
University of Arizona 75th anniversary papers, 1959-1961
AZ 069
University of Arizona
Correspondence, general admininstrative papers, and programs; citations, photographs and lists of recipients of Medallions of Merit; and newspaper clippings, and other items relating to the celebration of the 75th anniversary of the founding of the University of Arizona. Includes a 1960 address by Douglas D. Martin concerning the history of the University of Arizona.
2.7 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Historical Note
Program designed to commemorate the accomplishments of the University of Arizona in teaching, research, and public service.
Organization
This collection is organized into three series:
Series I: Correspondence and Administrative Papers, 1959-1960
Series II: Medallion Awards Materials, 1960-1961
Series III: Publicity, 1959-1961
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, general admininstrative papers, and programs; citations, photographs and lists of recipients of Medallions of Merit; and newspaper clippings, and other items relating to the celebration of the 75th anniversary of the founding of the University of Arizona. Includes a 1960 address by Douglas D. Martin concerning the history of the University of Arizona.
Access Terms
University of Arizona -- History
University of Arizona -- Anniversaries, etc.
University of Arizona -- Faculty
Clippings
Correspondence
Photographs
Container List
- Series I: Correspondence and Administrative Papers, 1959-1960
  - General Chairman: C. Zaner Lesher. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Formal announcement. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of meetings. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Club presidents. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arizona High Schools. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arizona Medical Association. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arizona Public School System. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arizona Council of Churches. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arizona Dental Associaiton. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Diocese of Tucson. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Congratulatory messages. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Publications: special material. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Territorial Graduates. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Civic Club meetings. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Wildcat special addition. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "A Brief History of the University of Arizona," address before the Tucson Kiwanis Club, by Douglas D. Martin. December 9, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Founders' Day. March 1, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Commencement. June 1, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Mexico at Mid-Century." December 10-16, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Honors convocation. December 4, 1959, December 2, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Homecoming. November 1959, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Programs of Events. (Box 2)
  - Catalog. 1959-1961 (Box 2)
  - President's Report. 1959-1960 (Box 2)
- Series II: Medallion Awards Materials, 1960-1961
  - Medallion Awards: citations. (Box 3)
  - Descriptive folder. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Awards: alphabetical list. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Awards: college and group list. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Award luncheons and dinner programs. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Acknowledgements, A-Z. (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Sample Plaque: 75th anniversary seal. (Box 4)
  - Medallion Awards: photographs. (Box 5)
- Series III: Publicity, 1959-1961
  - Clippings. May 1959-July 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
  - Publicity in various publications. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary folder. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous forms, promotional material, etc. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Banners. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Signs. (Box 7)